<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inner Demons, Meet Jesus</title>
    <description>Want to surrender your life to God? First, you&#39;ll need to introduce your demons to the Lord...</description>
    <link>http://change.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://change.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 20:45:25 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 20:45:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Are Worth It</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;For God so loved the world, that he gave his only Son, that whoever believes in him would not perish but have eternal life. (ESV, John 3:16)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For God so loved the world…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world. Those two words can make us as individuals feel completely removed from this special world that God loves. The world means &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; people, right? It means Christians and non-believers. It means the righteous and criminals. It means the poorest of the poor and richest of the rich. It’s says the world. It doesn’t say “For God so loved you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you sometimes forget that you are a part of this world God loves? He doesn’t draw a hard line through Earth and say, “These people are ok. But those people over there need to shape up if they want salvation and love.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He loves all of us, unconditionally, to the point of sacrifice. Every last one of us. That includes you. You. With all your mistakes and your flaws, with all your horrible thoughts and selfish ambitions. Can you imagine that someone who knows the worst things about you would still hang on a cross for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;? Your God did that. Not just for the world, not just for other people. But for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how much we are worth to God. Once we start accepting that we are loved that much, we’ll fight for ourselves as the Lord has fought for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look in the mirror and tell yourself, “I am worth it.” Repeat it. For an hour. For days. For weeks. As long as it takes for you to believe it. Ignore the voices that give you reasons why you are not worthy of His unconditional love. God knows those reasons and sacrificed for you anyway. How are you going to move forward from now? Are you going to believe you are worthy enough to abandon your inner demons? Or will you still believe you don’t deserve a better life?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://change.me/2016/you-are-worth-it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://change.me/2016/you-are-worth-it/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Understanding God</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make the Introduction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re not exactly prepared for what happens in our lives when we accept Christ as our Savior. We see the humble, the happy, and the God-fearing emanate the Holy Spirit, and we want to have what they have. We think being baptized will give us joy, peace, and rich faith. And then…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…nothing changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;life gets even harder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are trials. Confusion. Pain. Our greatest fears are thrown in our faces. We’re tempted to curse God and write Return to Sender on our gift of salvation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened? Weren’t we promised bliss, closeness to our Creator, and a softened heart? Now, we’re miserable, God is nowhere to be found, and our hearts are so hard that following Christ has become a chore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Do you not know that all of us who have been baptized into Christ Jesus were baptized into his death? We were buried therefore with him by baptism into death, in order that, just as Christ was raised from the dead by the glory of the Father, we too might walk in newness of life. (ESV, Romans 6:3-4)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we come to God as we are, we are giving ourselves to Him and essentially saying, “Here, take this brokenness and restore.” What we really want to add is, “But! But, leave those bits of me alone. I like those bits. I wanna keep those bits. K, thanks!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Those&lt;/em&gt; bits. Those fears, those idols, those traditions, those people, those sins that we would give anything not to have exposed, challenged, or taken away. Those bits. Those…&lt;em&gt;inner demons&lt;/em&gt;. If they stand in the way of serving God, those inner demons will be attacked. We can’t surrender to God when darkness has a hold on us. When we resist letting God purge that darkness from our life, we are locked in a struggle between those two opposing forces, and it’s up to us to make a choice which side we yield to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t have to fight these inner demons on our own. God does most of the work for us, but we have to introduce these demons to the Lord. Jesus is ready to meet them, and He is ready to pluck us out of their grasp. Ready to make that introduction?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://change.me/2016/inner-demons-meet-jesus/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://change.me/2016/inner-demons-meet-jesus/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Surrendering</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
